Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is chocolate therapy. Let me show
you how to make it. To make the
chocolate pudding base, we're using a
chocolate protein shake. I've been
loving these ones from Quest. 45 g of
protein for just 230 calories is
ridiculous. Then we're going to need
some cocoa powder, sweetener, salt, and
a little bit of Jell-O pudding mix.
Blend that all together and throw it in
your freezer for at least 16 hours. Then
we can take it out, run it under hot
water for about a minute, and then throw
it in the creamy on the light ice cream
setting. Now, I know what you're
thinking, Eli, you never use jello
pudding mix. And yeah, it's true. I
think it kind of sucks. But for a
chocolate pudding base, what do you
expect me to use? I'm still a hater,
don't get me wrong, but for this recipe,
it just works. Anyways, back to the
recipe. We are using three Oreo thins
with the cream removed. If you want to
keep the cream in, do it. It adds about
15 calories per Oreo, but that is
entirely up to you. Either way, this
recipe is going to be phenomenal.